bloomspot.com 2015-05-23

# Live Life Better - Bloomspot

Privacy Policy

Bloomspot Inc. takes very seriously the private nature of your personal information. This privacy policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit or use Bloomspot.com or our mobile application (collectively, the "Site"), as well as the information that we receive from partner companies or other third parties. Please read this notice carefully. 

Personal Information

In order to supply you with our e-mail services, we need your e-mail address. We collect your e-mail address when you provide it to us. In some cases, so that we may provide you with additional services, we may also request other personal information, such as your name, geographical location, and telephone number. We will never sell, rent or share your personal information, including your e-mail address, with any third parties for their marketing purposes without your express permission. We may, however, share your personal information (with our third party suppliers and others) for the purpose of delivering our e-mails and the Bloomspot service to you or as required, or allowed, by law. We may also share your personal information with our merchant partners when sharing this information may help our merchants fulfill a particular Bloomspot offer you’ve purchased. For example, we may share your personal information with merchants if the particular offer involves travel. And we may share your personal information in connection with a corporate change at Bloomspot, such as a merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale of assets. 

Non-Personal Information

We may also request non-personal information, such as annual income, buying preferences, or age, though providing this information is optional. We may use these data to improve our Site and/or to customize your experience at our Site so that we can show you content that we think you might be interested in, according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers who are interested in advertising through the emails we send out or on our Site. When we do share this information, we will share it in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person. 

Usage Information

In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, we (and/or our service providers) may also collect information about subscribers' use of our emails and our Site. This information is used to better understand how the services we provide are being used so that we can continually improve them. For example, this information will tell us how much time users spend using Bloomspot.com or our mobile application, from which other sites subscribers came, and to what other sites subscribers go when they leave Bloomspot. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, prepare for traffic load demands and more efficiently deliver our service. 

Bloomspot Mobile

You can access some or all of the Bloomspot service through mobile applications and mobile-optimized web pages. When you do, this privacy policy applies. We may collect information such as unique device identifiers for your mobile device, your screen resolution and other device settings, information about your location, and analytical information about how you use your mobile device. In some cases, we may ask your permission before collecting information through mobile channels. For example, we typically ask you to enter location data or give us permission to access location data that is associated to your device. 

Your Access Rights

You may review, update or modify certain of the personal information that is stored in your user account by logging in to the "My Account" section. Your right to delete your information is subject to our records retention policies. 

Choice/Opt-Out

If we ever send you information by e-mail concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with a link (typically at the bottom of the e-mail) through which you may request no further unsolicited promotional communications from us. 

Tracking

Like most sites, we make use of browser "cookies" on our Site. Cookies are small text files placed on your computer's or device’s hard disk by our server. They allow us to quickly check your status as a subscriber and facilitate access to your preferences. Some features / sections on Bloomspot – including navigating the Site as a logged-in user and having the Site recognize your preferred city – require you to accept a cookie in order to use them. You may choose not to accept cookies and still use the Site with limited functionality, but you won’t be able to take advantage of these features / sections. .We will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our Site or services. 

We also use transparent GIF images. We use these images to track the e-mails that we send out. 

Third Party Cookies

In the course of navigating to a third-party advertiser website, our advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. These cookies allow our third-party advertisers to identify traffic and/or a transaction as having been referred from Bloomspot. 

We also enable third party services, such as Google Analytics, to place or recognize a cookie on your browser. These cookies allow Bloomspot to gather analytics about site usage. 

Links to Other Sites

As part of the service, we may create links allowing you to access third party sites. We are not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and do not endorse these sites. Please consult those sites' individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information. 

Security

Bloomspot has established administrative, technical and physical controls that are designed to reasonably safeguard personal information. For example, the information described above is stored on restricted database servers and our employees may not access personal information if it is not reasonably necessary to do their job. 

Modification to this Privacy Policy

We may change this privacy policy, but we'll post any changes here. In some cases, we may also tell you about changes by additional means, such as by sending you an e-mail. 

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our Site in general, please contact us at Bloomspot Inc., 201 North Walnut St. DE1-1116 Wilmington, DE 19801 Fax: 1-855-602-5957. 

Last Updated: July 2013
